<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:webfeeds="http://webfeeds.org/rss/1.0"><channel><title>echo</title><link>https://www.inecho.cc/en/</link><description>Recent content on echo</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://www.inecho.cc/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>å…³äºŽ</title><link>https://www.inecho.cc/en/about/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2017 21:38:52 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.inecho.cc/en/about/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="hii-am-jackhttpswwwinechocc">ðŸ‘‹Hi,I am &lt;a href="https://www.inecho.cc/">Jack&lt;/a>&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>I am a cybersecurity practitioner and an amateur photographer. I enjoy exploring new fields and have a keen interest in photography, movies, and sports. In my spare time, I like to tinker with things that are useless but interesting. You can contact me via &lt;a href="mailto:rt7h.y.c@gmail.com">ðŸ“¨email&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I believe in lifelong learning and the integration of knowledge and action. I hope to keep learning and growing continuously, while also thinking and exploring during leisure time. Maintaining an open-minded attitude towards the world is important to me.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="about-the-website">ðŸ–¥ï¸About the Website&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>inecho.cc is actually my third domain name, and inecho is also my third personal website. Previously, the first two websites were &amp;ldquo;Multidimensional Can&amp;rdquo; using the WordPress framework, and a photography website using the Notion &amp;amp; Vercel solution. However, both of these websites did not persist for various reasons. After a year of website closure, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t resist building a new blog website, which is what you are seeing now on inecho.cc.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>inecho.cc is not derived from the meaning of &amp;ldquo;echo printing&amp;rdquo; in the bat command, but rather from the meaning of &amp;ldquo;echo resonance,&amp;rdquo; implying making sounds, hearing echoes, and self-improvement. Therefore, I hope to continue writing on inecho, producing more articles and engaging in deeper thoughts.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="last">â³Last&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>This website was created in January 2024, the year of Jiachen in the Chinese lunar calendar.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>